Guide to the Stan Steiner Papers, ca. 1940-1987 M0700
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series I. Subject Files
  - Native Americans -- Movements
    - Washington State: Forts Lawton & Lewis n.d. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Before Wounded Knee n.d. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Wounded Knee II n.d. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Russ Means at Wounded Knee Committee 1973 Oct (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Wounded Knee II: Transcription of AIM Tape "Inside the Siege" ["We Are Going Home: Testament of the Lakota People of Wounded Knee, II", TMs 49 pp.] n.d. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Wounded Knee II, 1973 [1 of 2] 1973 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Wounded Knee II, 1973 [2 of 2] 1973 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Wounded Knee: Trials and Defense 1973 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Wounded Knee: Election, Pine Ridge n.d. (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Native Americans -- Nation and Tribe
    - Akwesasne: White Roots of Peace 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Aleuts [Jones, Dorothy M. "Culture, Change, Race & Power: A Comparative Study of Two Aleut Villages," TMs, p.1-49] [1 of 4] n.d. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Aleuts [Jones, Dorothy M. "Culture, Change, Race & Power: A Comparative Study of Two Aleut Villages," TMs, pp. 50-99] [2 of 4] n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Aleuts [Jones, Dorothy M. "Culture, Change, Race & Power: A Comparative Study of Two Aleut Villages," TMs, pp. 100-149] [3 of 4] n.d. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Aleuts [Jones, Dorothy M. "Culture, Change, Race & Power: A Comparative Study of Two Aleut Villages," TMs, pp. 150-177] [4 of 4] n.d. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Anishinabi "Chippewa" [includes Sister M.Sirilla, O.S.B., "Looking into the Past," TMs, 8 pp.] [1 of 2] 1955-1973 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Anishinabi "Chippewa" [2 of 2] 1955-1973 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Apache n.d. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - California Indians [includes California v. Richard Oakes, et al., 1971] [re: Pitt River] 1968-1973 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Native [clippings re: Kahn-Tineta Horn] [1 of 2] 1959-1973 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Canadian Native [includes Indian Magazine 1968-1969, misc. pubs] [2 of 2] 1959-1973 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Cherokee: Georgia & Carolina n.d. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Cherokee: Oklahoma [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Cherokee: Oklahoma [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Conchiti n.d. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Creek n.d. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Eskimos 1966-1973 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Land of Havasupia and the Sierra Club 1975 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Hopis [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Hopis [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Hopis [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Menomine [includes: Orfield, Gary, "The War on Menominee Poverty," TMs, 16 pp.] 1964-1965, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Mohawk [1 of 2] 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Mohawk [2 of 2] 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Navajo: Arts 1960-1964, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Navajo: The Dineh [1 of 2] 1960-1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Navajo: The Dineh [2 of 2] 1960-1964 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Navajo Community College n.d. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Navajo Education n.d. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Navajo Health n.d. (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Navajo History [1 of 3] 1950-1968 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Navajo History [2 of 3] 1950-1968 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Navajo History [3 of 3] 1950-1968 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Navajo Lands 1959-1963, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Navajo Resources n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Navajo Tribal Council n.d. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Navajo Way n.d. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Navajo Women n.d. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Navajo Youth 1966-1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Navajo: Black Mesa Navajo [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Navajo: Black Mesa Navajo [includes: "Appalachia for the Indians?" TMs, 6 pp.] [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Navajo: Black Mesa Navajo [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Navajo: Black Mesa Contracts n.d. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Papago n.d. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Passamaquoddy c. 1967 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Pine Ridge 1966 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Rio Grande Pueblos n.d. (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Tesuque Pueblo and Colonias de Santa Fe n.d. (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Road to Santo Domingo Pueblo 1975 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Erlichman and the Pueblos "Penance" 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Seneca 1959-1970 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Rosebud Sioux 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - United Sioux 1958-1965 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Small Eastern Tribes 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Taos: Blue Lake [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Taos: Blue Lake [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Taos: Blue Lake [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Tesuque n.d. (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Tigua documents [1 of 4] 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Tigua documents [2 of 4] 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Tigua documents [3 of 4] 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Tigua documents [4 of 4] 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Tigua Tribe: Governor Pedrazza 1969 Jan (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Tigua History [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Tigua History [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Tigua Newsclips 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Tigua Photos n.d. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Tuscarora c. 1959 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Tuscarora of Carolina (Lumbees) 1972 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Paiutes (Nevada) n.d. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Pyramid Lake Utes n.d. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Southern Utes n.d. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Zuni n.d. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Zuni Ahaby: Da [Ahayu: da] n.d. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Native Americans -- Policy
    - American Indian Religious Freedom Act n.d. (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - ARCO Office of Indian Affairs n.d. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs: Bureaucracy n.d. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs: History n.d. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs: Programs n.d. (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs: Structure n.d. (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Citizenship 1969-1973 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - The Decline if [U.S. Rep. Wayne] Aspinall [D., Colorado] of Interior 1972 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - House of Represenatitves Interior Committee 1968 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Intertribal Ceremonial Gallup n.d. (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Omnibus Bill: Johnson Administration n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Politics: Elections n.d. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Politics: Tribal Governments n.d. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Politics: Washington D.C. n.d. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Relocation n.d. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Reorganization of BIA: Hickel, Walter J. & Bruce, Louis R. n.d. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Reorganization of BIA: Morton, Rogers 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Reorganization of BIA: Morton, Rogers 1973 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Senate Subcommittee on Indian Affairs n.d. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Southwestern Associaiton on Indian Affairs n.d. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Task Force on Indian Affairs: Kennedy Administration n.d. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Termination Policty: Eisenhower Administration [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Termination Policty: Eisenhower Administration [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Traders [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Traders [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - White House n.d. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Native Americans -- Publications
    - American Indian News -- NYC 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Cherokee Examiner n.d. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Eyapaha--Early Issues 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Ilotan-Indian League 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Indian Affairs: Newsletter of the Association on AmericanIndian Affairs, Inc. 1956-1968 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Indian Historian: Early Issues 1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Indian Voices -- University of Chicago -- Bob Thomas 1967 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - New Breed News -- Western Prisons n.d. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Pacific West Cherokee News 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Tundra Times -- First Issues 1962 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Tundra Times 1967 Aug 4 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - American Indian Horizon 1963-1966 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - The American Indian--San Francisco 1964-1966 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - American Indian Historical Society n.d. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Tribal Newspapers [1 of 2] 1960s (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Tribal Newspapers [2 of 2] 1960s (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Tribal Newspapers -- current 1970 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Tribal Newspapers -- cartoons n.d. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Native Americans -- Religion
    - Catholic Missions 1960-1984, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Christianity 1956-1973, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - The Christs of the Sun Dance 1962-1972, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - God Has Revelaed Himself in Indian Religion n.d. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Medicine Men & Politics 1968, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Medicine Men & Psychiatry 1964-1973, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Peyote Native American Church 1964-1967 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Prophecies - New 1966-1968, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - The Prophets 1962 Sept 17 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Protestant Missions 1966-1973, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Religion 1966-1972, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Shamanism n.d. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Native Americans -- Society
    - Alcohol & Other Drugs 1970-1973, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Bibliographies 1968-1969 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - City Aborigines 1960s (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Collectors 1964 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Community Economic Development 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Disease & Health 1957-1972 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Housing 1948-1966 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Latin Indians 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Laws & Orders 1959-1972 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Law Schools & Tribal Law 1969-1973, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - The Machines n.d. (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Mexican Indians 1973 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Native American Public T.V. Proposal n.d. (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Post War & Veterans n.d. (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Poverty: Spiritual and Material n.d. (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Private Industry 1964-1970, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Taxes 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Tribal Industry 1964-1974, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Tribal Middle Class 1968-1973, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Tribal Resources 1968, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Tribal Unemployment and Job Training 1963-1973, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Urban Indian n.d. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Urban Indian Centers n.d. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Village Industry n.d. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - The Word [1 of 2] 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - The Word [2 of 2] 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Native Americans -- Testamonies
    - Asa Bazgibiidag - "Kee Shelton's Mother" n.d. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Grace Black Elk -- Ogalalla n.d. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Mifanway Shonatona -- Indian Lovers and Friends n.d. (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Ward, Bob, "Testament of a Trader" 1974-1975, Winter (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Anne Wauneka n.d. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Native Americans -- Treaties
    - Battle of Washington, D.C. 1972 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Black Hills Treaty Rights n.d. (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Eagle Feather Busts 1975 Feb. (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Hunting and Fishing Rights 1951-1968 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Pueblo Treaty of 1850 and related papers [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Pueblo Treaty of 1850 and related papers [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Native Americans -- Women
    - Family Life 1968-1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Native Women -- American Indian Women's League c. 1969 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Native Women -- Child Trade 1967-1973 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Native Women -- Contemporary 1964-1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Native Women -- "To Have Been..." (Shirley Witt) n.d. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Women -- Historic n.d. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Native Americans -- Miscellaneous
    - Atlantis and Lost Tribes n.d. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Birth of the People n.d. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Catalogs n.d. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - The Corporate Missioniaries [includes correspondence with Sam Gardipe] n.d. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - The Hymmie Hochwasser [Highwater, Jamake] n.d. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Statistics n.d. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Theories of Asian Origin n.d. (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Maps n.d. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Rainbow Lakes [Florida] c. 1971 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Indian Materials 1972-1985 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous articles n.d. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Negro Culture
    - Black Power: Definitions and Aims n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Culture of Ancient Africa 1958 Oct 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Contemporary Africa 1950 Oct 15-1958 Nov 6, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Jim Crow & The Arts 1945 Mar 27 -1962 Apr 4, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Negro Art n.d. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - The Negro & The Arts 1946 Jan 26-1954 Feb 8, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Negro in the Film 1946 Mar14-1958 Sept, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Negro Literature 1942 Feb 21-1959 Feb 8 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Negro Poetry 1941 July 6-1959 Apr 26 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Negro Theatre & Actors 1946 Oct 8 -1961 Sept (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - New Mexico
    - New Mexico Air 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Copper Strike 1967 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - New Mexico Ecology [1 of 5] 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - New Mexico Ecology [2 of 5] 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - New Mexico Ecology [3 of 5] 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - New Mexico Ecology [4 of 5] 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - New Mexico Ecology [5 of 5] 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - New Mexico Economics [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - New Mexico Economics [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - New Mexico Economics [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - New Mexico Economy n.d. (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - New Mexico Farming c. 1956 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - New Mexico: General [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - New Mexico: General [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - New Mexico: General [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - New Mexico: General [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - New Mexico: General [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - New Mexico: General [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - New Mexico: General [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - New Mexico: General [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - New Mexico: Manufacturing n.d. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - New Mexico: Mining 1970 -1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Miscellany n.d. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Miscellany n.d. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - New Mexico: Nuclear bombs n.d. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - New Mexico: Oil n.d. (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - New Mexico: Politicos n.d. (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Pueblo Christmas n.d. (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Pueblo dances [from the New York Times] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - New Mexico: Real Estate n.d. (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - New Mexico: Santa Fe material n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - New Mexico: Santa Fe n.d. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - New Mexico: Tourismo n.d. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - New Mexico: Water n.d. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Politics
    - American Security Council 1958 -1962 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs n.d. (Box 40, Folder 6)
      includes: "The Bureau," TMs, 23 pp.
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs, Reorganization of: Udall, Stewart L. n.d. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - O.A.S. [Secret Army Organization, Algeria] 1962 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - F.B.I.: history n.d. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - F.B.I. and military 1961 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - F.B.I. and politics 1962 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - F.B.I. and Rightists n.d. (Box 40, Folder 12)
      includes: Newberry, Mike. "The Underground world of J. Edgar Hoover," TMs, 11 pp.
    - F.B.I.: Hoover, J. Edgar n.d. (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - The Military and ISM [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 40, Folder 14)
      includes: Newberry, Mike. "Rattling the sabre 'behind enemy lines," The Worker, 1960 Sept.
    - The Military and ISM [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - The Military and ISM [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - The Military and politics 1960s (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Walker, Edwin A., General 1961 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Right to Work Committee [1 of 3] 1943 -1963 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Right to Work Committee [2 of 3] 1943 -1963 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Right to Work Committee [3 of 3] 1943 -1963 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Truman budget messages 1948 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Urban Office of Economic Opportunity 1967 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - War on Poverty n.d. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - War on Poverty [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - War on Poverty [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Welfare system, food plans, attitudes n.d. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Forrestal, James n.d. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Gannett, Frank n.d. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Hoover, Herbert n.d. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Lehman, Herbert n.d. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Stassen, Harold n.d. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Truman, Harry n.d. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur n.d. (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Pew, [Joseph Newton], Hutton, etc. n.d. (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Corruption: Congress n.d. (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Politics -- Lobbies
    - Chamber of Commerce 1961 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Liberty Lobby [1 of 3] 1961 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Liberty Lobby [2 of 3] 1961 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Liberty Lobby [3 of 3] 1961 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - National Association of Manufacturers [N.A.M.] 1959 -1962 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - National Committee for Economic Freedom 1961 -1962 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - National Economic Council 1941 -1961 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - National Education Program (Searcy, AR) 1961 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - National Rifle Association [N.R.A.], etc. [1 of 2] 1964 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - National Rifle Association [N.R.A.], etc. [2 of 2] 1964 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Old Age Health Insurance 1962 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - We the People n.d. (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous lobbies 1960 -1961 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Politics -- Left Wing Organizations
    - American Labor Party 1942 -1948 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Communist Party 1929 -1939 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Communist Party, 1939 - 1945 1941 -1944 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Communist Party: leaders n.d. (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Communist Party, USA 1946 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Early American radicals n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Left sectarianism n.d. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Progressive Party [1 of 2] 1947 -1949 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      newspaper clippings
    - Progressive Party [2 of 2] 1947 -1949 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      pamphlets
    - Trotskyists 1936 -1944 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Politics -- Right Wing Organizations
    - America First Party n.d. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - American Conservative Union [A.C.U.] 1965 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - American Legion 1962 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - American National Party n.d. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Americans for Constitutional Action [A.C.A.] 1962 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Americans for National Security 1963 -1973 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - American Nazi Party 1961 -1963 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - American Youth Groups: Junior Achievement n.d. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Anti-Semitism [1 of 2] 1959 -1962 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Anti-Semitism [2 of 2] 1959 -1962 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Anti-U.N. Drive 1959 -1962 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      includes multiple articles by Mike Newberry
    - Birch Society campaigns 1961 -1964 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Birch Society: campaigns on 1961 -1962 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Christian Freedom Foundations n.d. (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Citizens' Council 1961 -1965 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - College Conservatives 1961 -1962 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Committee for Constitutional Government 1950 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Defenders of American Liberty 1962 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Fighting American Nationalists [F.A.N.] 1962 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - History of American Fascism: current [1 of 2] 1959 -1964 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - History of American Fascism: current [2 of 2] 1961 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Ku Klux Klan and armed groups 1960s (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Minutemen and Right armed groups n.d. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - National Indignation Convention 1961 -1962 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Nationalist Party 1962 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Nazi Youth n.d. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Project Alert 1961 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Public Action 1961 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      includes: Newberry, Mike. "Swanky Fascists: There's money in hate'," The Worker (1961 May 14)
    - Renaissance Party n.d. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Schools and texts: right and education 1947 -1964 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Soldiers of the Cross: Goff, Kenneth 1962 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - States Rights Party 1960 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      includes: Newberry, Mike. "'Mobile hate' units of the South: The National States Rights Party," TMs, 6 pp.
    - Supreme Court and right 1961 -1962 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Ultra International 1962 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Ultras and Africa n.d. (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - California Ultras 1962 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Illinois and Midwest Ultras 1962 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Labor and the Ultras 1961 -1962 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - New England Ultras 1961 -1962 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - New York Ultras 1960 -1964 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Northwest Ultras 1962 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Ultra racism and white supremacy 1959 -1962 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Romney and Ultras 1962 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Ultras and Southern Politics 1961 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Southwest Ultras 1961 -1962 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Texas Ultras 1961 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Ultra youth 1959 -1961 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Ultras and Big Business 1961 -1964 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Ultras on the Farm: American Farm Bureau Federation, etc. 1962 -1963 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Welfare State-ism: Relief vs. Right 1961 -1962 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Y.A.F. [Young Americans for Freedom] 1961 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Y.A.F. [Young Americans for Freedom] 1962 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Y.A.F. [Young Americans for Freedom] 1961 -1963 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Young Conservatives n.d. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Young Republicans 1961 -1963 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Politics -- Red Hunting
    - American Opinion n.d. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Death of Rosenbergs 1953 June (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Goff-Oliver Survival Sheet n.d. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - House Un-American Activities Committee [H.U.A.C.]: Dies, Martin 1947 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - House Un-American Activities Committee [H.U.A.C.]: Thomas, J. Parnell 1945 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - House Un-American Activities Committee [H.U.A.C.]: Walter, Francis [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - House Un-American Activities Committee [H.U.A.C.]: Walter, Francis [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 44, Folder 12)
      includes: Newberry, Mike. "Un-American Committee's Rep. Walters Joins Fascists Anti-CP Propaganda," TMs, 5 pp.
    - Human Events.--Vol. 19, no. 4 1962 Jan. 27 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Informers of the 1950s 1943 -1947 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Life Lines n.d. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Loyalty Oaths n.d. (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Matthews, J. B. 1949 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - McCarran Act: Subversive Activities Control Board 1962 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - McCarran Act [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - McCarran Act [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - McCarran Act [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - National Council on American Education: Zoll 1954 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Red-Hunting: State Committees 1947 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Senate Internal Security Subcommittee 1961 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Smith [Howard] Act 1942 -1961 (Box 44, Folder 25)